("Me & Bobby McGee" by Janis Joplin)
♪ Busted flat in Baton
Rouge waiting for a train ♪
♪ I was feeling near
as faded as my jeans ♪
♪ Bobby thumbed a diesel
down just before it rained ♪
♪ And rode us all the way to New Orleans ♪
♪ I pulled my harpoon out
of my dirty red bandana ♪
♪ I was playing soft while
Bobby sang the blues ♪
♪ Windshield wipers slapping time ♪
♪ I was holding Bobby's hand in mine ♪
♪ We sang every song that driver knew ♪
♪ Freedom's just another word
for nothing left to lose ♪
♪ Nothing don't mean nothing
honey if it ain't free now now ♪
♪ And feeling good was easy
Lord when he sang the blues ♪
♪ You know feeling good
was good enough for me ♪
♪ Good enough for me and my Bobby McGee ♪
♪ From the Kentucky coal
mines to the California sun ♪
♪ Hey Bobby shared the
secrets of my soul ♪
♪ Through all kinds of weather ♪
♪ Through everything that we done ♪
♪ Hey Bobby baby kept me from the cold ♪
♪ One day up near Salinas
Lord I let him slip away ♪
♪ He's looking for that home
and I hope he finds it ♪
♪ But I'd trade all of my tomorrows
for one single yesterday ♪
♪ To be holding Bobby's
body next to mine ♪
♪ Freedom's just another word
for nothing left to lose ♪
♪ Nothing and that's all
that Bobby left me yeah ♪
♪ And feeling good was easy
Lord when he sang the blues ♪
♪ Hey feeling good was good
enough for me hmm hmm ♪
♪ Good enough for me and my Bobby McGee ♪
♪ La la la la la la la
la la la la la la la ♪
♪ La la la la la Bobby McGee ♪
♪ La la la la la la la la la la ♪
♪ La la la la la Bobby McGee la ♪
♪ La La la la la la la la la ♪
♪ Hey now Bobby now Bobby McGee yeah ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na
na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ Hey now Bobby now Bobby McGee yeah ♪
♪ Lord I called him my
lover I called him my man ♪
♪ I said called him my lover
just the best I can and come on ♪
♪ And and a Bobby oh
and a Bobby McGee yeah ♪
♪ Lo lo lo lo lo lo lo lo lo lo lo lo ♪
♪ Hey hey hey Bobby McGee lord ♪
♪ La da la la la la da la la la la la ♪
♪ Hey hey hey Bobby McGee yeah ♪